I'm about to interview one of the most legendary
and richest entrepreneurs of all time and his name
you know him it's Dana White who am I here with
today Dana White and how did you get rich I sell
fights for a living what do you mean I'm the
CEO of the UFC and you're running a billion dollar
company multi-billion dollar company a multi-billion dollar
company guys Dana White took a failing mma
company and turned it into a multi-billion dollar
business you know that business it's the UFC in
this video I'm going to be doing something
absolutely insane guys I'm going to be flying
out to Las Vegas to the UFC headquarters to
go meet up with and interview the legendary Dana
White but before we do that look I'm not in
Las Vegas right now as you can see I'm in Beverly
Hills and before meeting up with Dana I'm going
to be hitting the streets to go find the richest
people that live out here in Beverly Hills to
figure out how they got rich and how you can
become wealthy and build generational wealth just like them
so this video is about to be insane from
start to finish so stay tuned until the end
that being said let's get this video on the way
so look as you can
see look we're at the Beverly
Wilshire hotel some of the richest people in
LA they come here for business meetings and whatnot
and somebody that I interviewed before that made
over a hundred million dollars he did two billion
in sales throughout his career actually just pulled
up to the valet is this your Rolls Royce
yeah I have the biggest business media team on
the entire world called the school of hard knocks right
interview guys like Shaq Mark Cuban what did you what
did you do get a Rolls Royce I invented gel
nails 1981. what's the most important thing about being
a business media team in the world is that
most amount of money you made this single year made
over 100 million we're going to see if we can
go track him down and get a part two interview
with him to figure out how he got rich and became
one of the richest men out here in Beverly Hills
you guys come on excuse me sir sir how did you
become wealthy you know I already told you
I invented gel nails so you're an inventor I'm
the inventor of gel nails yeah how much money did
you make I made over 100 million dollars in my
career can I get a minute of your time real quick
sure you can why not so give me the most life
changing advice you ever received on money
that made you the nine-figure entrepreneur that you
are today give me the best money advice you ever
got throughout your career I go to work every day
at five o'clock I'm 71 years old it's 95
percent perspiration and five percent luck the best advice
I can give you is keep trying get out there
and do it when did you learn you weren't going
to get rich working for anybody else I knew that when I
was 24 years old I knew I had to be a boss
what's the worst financial decision you made the
worst financial decision I ever made was probably
when I met the owners of google they wanted
me to put five thousand dollars into the search engine
and soon as far as I know that didn't
happen I spent a million dollars not even shrimp I
spent a million dollars in my first app on
google and I none of those people really Jason
Dreier from the
という
people
know
as
I
told
Two things I was the
most successful out of my business.
One was tax-free bonds.
When everybody wanted to go in the stock market,
when I was 30 years old, they told me you
can get a 12% return.
I looked at California state tax-free bonds, paid 5%.
I've been doing that.
I started with 2 million.
I have it up to 50 million in tax-free bonds.
Never cashed one in.
It's guaranteed by the state of California.
The other is industrial real estate.
When I was in Inca Magazine in
1987, the number one guy was Mitch Schlossberg.
He was in Cleveland.
I stayed up with him
until 3 o'clock in the morning.
He asked me if I was gay.
I said, why do you think I'm gay?
He said, well, you won't leave my room.
I said, I never met anybody my age
that's 100 times richer than me, smarter than me.
Teach me real estate.
He said, I'll teach you real estate.
I said, buy investment property, put 50%
down, never leverage it, never sell it.
I said, well, how the fuck do you make money?
He said, you idiot.
Your mortgage goes down, your payments go up
on the property, and you give it to your
kids.
That's why it's called real estate.
You know they don't teach that in school, right?
They don't teach that in
school, but they do teach it.
In Hard Knocks, in the school of Hard
Knocks, because that's why people are listening here,
because they want to see successful people.
How important was the entity structuring
when you were building your company?
The energy structure for building it?
It was very important.
Did you have an LLC when you started your business?
I didn't have an LLC.
It was a partnership at the time.
But I gave one-
Was that a mistake, not having the entity structure?
I should have had an LLC.
You should always have an LLC for liability.
Why?
If you get sued, you don't want them to
take your house, your car, and all your personal.
But the key is, again, everybody should do it.
When you go in business, you never know if
a kid is going to swallow something and you're
going to get sued.
An LLC is what covers you.
They could sue your corporation.
And thank God you can bankrupt that
corporation and still keep your personal assets.
So why wouldn't you do it?
I tell everybody this.
The most affordable way to start a business
in today's world and start an LLC is through
a company that I use.
It's called Bizzy.
And it allowed us to start a business
overnight, not years like everybody thinks it takes.
And we built a multi-million dollar
business in just a couple of years.
It's very important.
I love that.
In a sense, you don't even really need a lawyer.
You don't need a lawyer.
You don't need a loan.
You got amazing advice, Tony.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
And you got amazing following.
But guess what, though?
We got to make some money together.
Oh, I've been trying with you, kid.
How much are we going to make together?
I got ideas for you that will blow your mind.
How much?
How much can we make?
I don't know what you're making now, but I
think you can make 50, 60 million a year with
my ideas.
Let's make it happen.
Guys, we just interviewed that
hundred million dollar entrepreneur again.
And did you hear what he just said?
His biggest regret in business was not
setting up an LLC from the get go.
And why?
Because it protects you from
so much as a business owner.
And he's right.
Let me explain.
Look, too many entrepreneurs, they build
great businesses, even amazing businesses, but they
skip the foundation, which is the most important part.
That structure, that LLC or S-Corp
is what keeps your personal assets safe.
It lowers your taxes and it makes
your business real rather than just an idea.
And that's exactly why I tell all people
in business, you do not need a lawyer.
You need busy.
Busy is the platform every entrepreneur should start with.
And why?
Because it's the most affordable and
easiest way to start your business.
There's no lawyers.
There's no confusing paperwork involved.
There's no stress.
You can literally create your LLC or S-Corp
and start your business in under 10 minutes.
And you get a free registered agent
for a year and lifetime compliance alerts.
So you never miss a filing.
And look, guys, here's the thing.
I'm not just telling you this.
I'm telling you this because I actually use busy.
I built my own multimillion
dollar company through using busy.
And it gave me the foundation to scale
without the legal side of things holding me back,
which is what so many business owners struggle with.
So if you're serious about turning your idea
into a business, you're going to need a business
that does not wait any longer.
All you have to do is go down, click
the link in the description of this video and start
your business with busy today.
And it'll be the smartest
first step that you ever take.
With that being said, let's go get our next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, how old were you when you became a millionaire?
Twenty seven years old.
And what line of business are you in?
Well, I'm an entrepreneur, but I've had many businesses.
What happened at 27?
Twenty seven.
I did a big deal and
I had to put together two people.
And my commission on them?
My commission on it was 48 million bucks.
You did that yourself?
Yeah.
So it's safe to say that dealmakers
can really make the money in today's world.
Dealmakers, they make a lot of money.
So you don't have to be the smartest guy,
but if you can connect the right two people
together and make money out of
it, you're going to make money.
The smartest guy is the guy who's closest to God.
When you keep God first, you
can get whatever you want in life.
Did you always believe in God?
Always believed in God.
My father's a minister, but as I
got older, I had a near death experience.
Four years ago, I had double pneumonia and
COVID and they gave me 24 hours to live.
And here I am today, five years later.
So you think it was
God that got you through that?
No, I don't think it was God.
I didn't know it was God because I had
five doctors telling my family I was going to die
that night.
So what would you say to
somebody out there that's questioning their belief?
They don't think that God's actually there.
What would you say to them?
I would say God is here.
No matter what you want in life, you
know, we all go through problems in life.
And once we get past that problem, no matter
what the problem is, we always get over it.
Once we get over that problem, we have
to figure out how do we do it?
Where did it come from?
So you got to backtrack and say,
okay, how did I get here today?
You know, I own a huge technology company.
It's worth $1.2 billion.
So you're a billionaire?
Well, on paper, yes.
That's amazing.
On paper.
I'm a billionaire.
Jeffrey Phillips.
No why.
Just Jeffrey without a why.
Don't ask why.
So what does it take to
build out a billion dollar company?
You know what?
I'm blessed.
Deals come to me.
It's like you guys approaching me right now.
So you're saying once you build that
credibility, it starts to come to you.
Once you build that credibility, your
trust in God, everything comes to you.
I know right now I can ask
for anything I want and I'll get it.
So it's safe to say faith is
at the center of every decision you make.
Faith is at the center of every decision.
I have all that I have only because of God.
What type of tech company are you running today?
Gaming.
Have you ever blackjack?
Yeah.
You know blackjack with the bonus
round where you put money there?
Yes.
I own all the patents to those.
Are you kidding me?
So when you play and lose, I get paid.
Oh my goodness right now.
And see once again, that just happened by a blessing.
But that's a lesson in itself right there
because patents, if you own the patent, you
can make a lot of money.
If you own the patents to anything,
you can make a lot of money.
You don't have to work.
How do you get the patent though?
That's where God comes in.
I was in Vegas.
I had a TV show that I was on
for two years and somebody recognized me and they said,
oh my gosh, I was just at home
watching a TV show and I'm sitting there.
I meet with this person.
She tells me her dad has these.
Patents over two or three years period.
I meet with her father who owned video
poker and he says, listen, I've got these patents
for this new version of
blackjack that's going to come out.
This is back in 2018 and
I ended up buying it from him.
And here we are today.
Did you have anybody that doubted you
to build that gaming company centered around blackjack
and do a billion dollar company?
You had to ask him,
did people think you were crazy?
People still think I'm crazy.
They do.
Are you crazy?
A little bit, maybe.
Yeah, of course.
Just a little bit.
I live in LA.
I'm crazy.
You have to be a
little crazy to be successful though.
To be that successful, you have to.
You do.
I grew up in Buffalo, New York and I'm a millionaire
at 27 and get to this point at 58 where I've
got a company that's worth a billion plus.
Like I said, it's only
God that can get you here.
So you got to have faith and belief.
If I say, you know what,
I'm going to own that building.
I may not have the revenue to do
it, but I'm going to have that building.
You come back a year from
now, I'm going to have it.
You know what's going to happen?
The universe is going to open.
And when I start telling you I'm going
to own that building and start telling other
people, I'll tell one person, they'll say, Hey,
I know the guy that owns it and he's
looking to sell it.
This is how my entire life has worked.
You know, to do that $48 million deal.
I was at a restaurant like this and I was
sitting at the table and it was a casino deal
and a woman had chair next to me.
She says, Hey, I'm trying to put together a casino.
She's talking to someone else and I'm over listening.
I say, Hey, I got a
guy that want to buy a casino.
Her investors put up $450 million.
My commission on it, my take was $48 million.
I was 27 turned 28.
I want to challenge you right now.
Take me back to the most
life changing conversation you ever had.
What is the greatest advice
you ever received throughout your career?
I was from a doctor.
I was sick in Vegas and I was trying
to raise money to do my first TV show.
And I had given up and the
doctor said, you got to believe in yourself.
He said, stop investing other things and invest in yourself.
Once I started to invest in
myself and started believing everything happened.
Sometimes the most unconventional circumstances can
lead to the greatest pieces of advice
because it's from a doctor and your business doctor.
Your business guy.
Yeah, I am.
You can learn something from everybody.
That's why I love this channel because
there's people from so many different backgrounds,
so many different businesses, but we can learn
little bits and pieces from everybody on this
in this earth.
Oh yeah.
You can learn from everybody.
The homeless man on the street, you can learn,
you know, and I talk to homeless people all
the time and I do learn a lot from him.
Did you ever go broke?
Of course.
Are you kidding?
I was born broke.
So you lost that 48 million.
Oh, are you kidding?
I lost that 30 years ago.
But you made it all back.
I make it all back.
And if I lose it again
today, I'll make it back again.
You would have how?
Like I said, having faith
and belief and believe in myself.
And one thing I do have is a creative mind.
So I know how to make anything happen.
How old are you now?
I'm just starting 58.
If me and you died tomorrow and you had
one more guiding principle to leave with the younger
generation, what would that be?
Believe in God.
I love it, man.
I appreciate you, man.
I got to go.
God bless you, man.
Keep it up.
Could I give you my contact?
All right.
We got two moguls in Beverly Hills.
It's time to head out to Las
Vegas to get the mogul, Dana White.
There's no better promoter and marketer
in sports than Dana White himself.
He turned the UFC from a
failing company to a multi-billion dollar business.
So let's go fly out to Las Vegas right
now and go meet up with the legend himself, you
guys.
Come on.
All right, how are you doing?
We're going to go see Dana.
I just called his assistant.
You guys are good.
Right to the love.
He's just going to come and grab you guys, okay?
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
All right, you guys.
We just got to the UFC Performance Institute.
We're about to interview the man
himself, Dana White, out here, you guys.
Come on.
All right, you guys.
This is a full circle moment for me.
I want you guys to understand.
Listen, I grew up watching all the UFC fights.
I grew up watching Dana
White promote all of the fights.
Conor McGregor, Floyd Mayweather, you name it, you guys.
So this is a full circle moment.
We're about to be linking up
and interviewing the legend himself, Dana White.
Come on.
How are you, James?
It's great to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Have you guys been to the UFC before?
No.
I've been to the UFC before.
You want to do a little walk-around?
Yeah, that'd be awesome.
It'd be cool.
This is the UFC headquarters.
This is where all of
our guys come to cut weight.
Also, quite a few UFC fighters live in Vegas,
so they work out here on a daily basis.
Hi, guys.
Welcome to the Performance Institute.
My name is Vanessa.
James.
Great to meet you.
I fight in the UFC.
Where are you from?
Austin, Texas.
Let's go.
Yeah, Austin.
That's awesome.
Do you do social media?
I do, yeah.
Are you that guy that asks
people what they do, like the millionaires?
Yeah, that's it.
Like, hey, watch me make all your money.
Dude, that's so dope.
I watch your all the time.
Thank you so much.
Congratulations on all your success, man.
Congratulations.
It's really great to meet you.
Have some fun, you guys.
Yeah, if you want to have some fun
upstairs, I'd be glad to beat you up.
Hey, let me get half of it.
Hey!
I got you.
Bye, guys.
How you doing, Dana?
Great to meet you.
You too.
Pleasure.
Who's going to bring in?
We'll do it in the bar.
South Bay, man.
Right here?
Yes, sir.
Absolutely.
Let me come on the ...
Got you, my man.
100% deaf in that ear.
It'll be an awkward interview when I can't hear you.
Yeah, man.
It's all good.
Where you from?
Austin, Texas.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, I live in Austin.
Grew up in the DC area, but
we've been in Austin the last five years.
I started the channel my freshman year at
the University of Texas and grew it to about
17 million followers across all platforms
and been able to end it.
But I got to tell you, this is a
special one for you because you're definitely on my Mount
Rushmore of entrepreneurs.
I grew up, you can ask him, watching you promote-
Thank you.
We had the UFC posters in our
basement in the background five years ago.
That's awesome, man.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
I got one rule for the interview, though.
There's no holding back.
We're going to give the younger
generation the secrets to becoming successful.
I don't hold back.
I know you don't.
It's a good rule.
Who am I here with today?
Dana White.
How did you get rich?
I sell fights for a living.
What do you mean?
I'm the CEO of the UFC.
You're running a billion dollar company.
Multi-billion dollar company.
A multi-billion dollar company.
Take me back before the UFC.
You were a bellman at a hotel in Boston.
What was the moment when you
realized, I'm meant for more than this?
It wasn't was I meant for more than this.
It was just like, this isn't me.
This isn't what I want to
do for the rest of my life.
And not to shit on jobs like that, because
a lot of my friends still work at the hotel
and stuff.
It just wasn't for me.
I didn't like anything about it.
And I said, you know what?
I want to be in the fight business,
which was probably the dumbest idea ever at that
time.
And if it didn't work out, I
could always go back and be a bellman.
When you're 19, 20, 21,
even in your 30s, take risks.
You have to take risks.
Do it before you have the responsibility.
I didn't have my kids until I was like 33.
And you mortgaged your future on athletics.
At the time, a failing MMA company.
What is it that you saw
in the UFC that nobody else saw?
Yeah.
Well, not just me.
Me and my partners all
felt that we loved the storylines.
We thought that the fighting
was way more exciting than boxing.
And we loved boxing.
And we believed that we could take all
the things that we hated about boxing and loved
about boxing and make this thing
as perfect as we possibly could.
And you disrupted the fight business.
So let's talk to an entrepreneur right now.
They're trying to disrupt an industry.
What would your advice be to them?
Yeah, that's a great question.
I think that when you get to the fight business,
you're going to be able to do a lot of things.
You get into, you know, especially back then
before social media or the internet or any
of that stuff, there was a lot of old
money and a lot of young people didn't have the
opportunity to make money.
It's the wild, wild west now.
It's a free for all.
There are so many opportunities
for disrupting, like you said.
And basically what you do is you
go in and break all the rules.
People will always tell you, oh, this
will never work or they're too big.
You can't.
People said, you'll never be bigger than boxing.
People have been telling me that for 25 years.
And yes.
You can be.
You got to get in there and you
literally have to shake up and break the rules.
Just because something has been the way it
has been for a hundred years, doesn't mean
it can't be changed.
Can't be different.
Can't be better.
Was there a time when you were growing
the UFC, when you thought to yourself, this is
all going to collapse.
And if so, how did you get through that?
Yeah.
I mean, you'll go through that all the time.
It's not like you just get here
and it's like, all right, we're here.
I just did a new deal with Paramount.
How much?
$7.7 billion deal with Paramount.
And I'm going into this new Paramount
deal in January on a fresh slate.
I have to go out and prove myself again.
You have to keep proving yourself every year.
And like I have this ritual now, every Christmas I
go to Italy and I'm on a boat in the middle
of Italy and just take like eight to 10 days.
And by seven, eight, nine, I'm like,
I'm ready to kick next year's ass.
So you literally have to get up
every day and go out and prove yourself.
Even when you buy industry standards or buy
other people's idea of success, you have to
keep grinding and you have to keep going.
I saw you were just talking about in
a press conference, you were asked about, you know,
how you do.
How are you going to compete with the other promoters?
And you think way bigger than everybody else.
How long-term are you thinking?
It's hilarious.
So these promoters are like, oh,
can't wait to compete with me.
You guys have been doing this for, you know,
10, 20, 30, 40, 50 years, depending on the
promoter.
And you're still in the same place.
You don't think big enough.
The way that I look at when I talk about
competing, first of all, I love to compete against myself.
Are you afraid of competition?
Have you ever been afraid of competition?
No, I love competition.
I love everything about fighting and competition,
no matter what it is, is a fight.
I mean, I just did the 60 Minutes interview
and they asked me, we asked around about you
and what do you think people said?
And I knew they were going to say loyal, right?
And what do you think other people said?
Bully.
Anybody that said I was a bully
tried to compete with me and lost.
They got their asses kicked.
Yeah.
I mean, that's how it works.
If you want to pick a fight, there's
a winner and a loser in a fight.
And I love that.
So you know, if you come and say
you want to compete against us, let's compete.
You brought up loyal though.
How important is it to keep your word in business?
It's everything.
Your word is not just business.
It's business and life.
Your word is everything in life.
For instance, I mean, I talk about this one
all the time too, but we went through COVID
because I wasn't laying off any employees, you
know, but when you are a massive company
like we are now, there's
a lot of miles to feed.
And if there's no revenue coming in, you
got to make some horrible decisions that I wasn't
going to make.
Well, listen, we're either this mother is a battleship.
We go into battle every day and we're
either all going down together or not at all.
So it's like the scariest time in our lifetime.
And I'm much older than you.
Scariest time in our lifetime.
You know?
You have all these employees and these people who
show up every day and work hard for you
and the shit hits the fan.
It's the scariest time in the world.
And just because of money, you're going
to just let all these people go.
Good luck to you, everybody.
I hope you can figure out groceries and
toilet paper and whatever else it is that everybody
needed during COVID, but good luck.
And then everything turns around and comes back.
What do you think?
Who the would want to work for you
when that's the way you treated the people that
were with you, you know?
And real quick for my audience, for the
people that don't understand this during COVID, every
major sports organization, they were shutting down.
You decided to go out to the Middle
East and you pioneered the business out there.
Why did you do that?
And was it just the innovator in you that
was like, I'm not letting this happen to my
company?
Yeah.
You know, I had to distribute my product
to ESPN and other networks around the world.
And first of all, I had an arena next door.
Just built my own arena.
And the governor here would
not let me use my arena.
Social distancing.
And I said, then I just
need to, I kept thinking island.
I need an island where I
can go out somewhere that has infrastructure.
And all I have to do is put on fights
and beam the signal up to all of our partners.
You can't tell me that that's
not possible, that we can't do that.
Not to mention the fact that I have this philosophy.
I grew up in the seventies and eighties.
It's 2025.
Anything is possible.
Don't tell me something can't be done.
Everything can be done.
That's the other word I
don't like around here is no.
No and we can't.
One of the things you've talked about
throughout the interview is the importance of people.
Surrounding yourself with the right people.
When I look at you and
your network, your business partners are billionaires.
You're great friends with president Trump.
Some of the most successful, some
of the richest people in the world.
If it boils down to one trait, think
about the most successful people that you know,
what do they all have in common?
Consistency.
Consistency is the key to everything in life.
Whether it's getting up and building the
business, getting in shape, working on different relationships,
you have to be a consistent person,
but you have to be driven too.
To have consistency, you have to have drive.
And I say this all the time.
I see a lot of this younger generation.
I don't know.
They just seem weak to
me in a lot of ways.
So let me ask you this.
I'm 23.
How old are you?
Yeah.
I'm 56.
So whose generation works harder, yours or mine?
Oh, my generation will run you mother
over and then back over you again.
But you think it's easy
to stand out in my generation?
A hundred percent.
How can somebody stand out?
Look at what you've done.
Look at your success and look at what you've done.
You know how you did it.
You know, you worked your ass off from the outside.
It's like these people, I hear these
kids, oh, I want to be an influencer.
Do you even understand?
Like I'm close to the milk boys.
These kids are on the road nonstop
grinding, working, taking your own money and reinvesting
in your business and reinvesting
in yourself, believing in yourself.
And like you said, being a disruptor.
But you know, but kid, if
I talk to somebody like you.
You're 23.
Yeah.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
That's why you're asking all the right
questions because you know what it takes.
A lot of the kids in
this generation, I don't see it.
So there's never been more opportunity for guys like you.
I'm going to challenge you right now.
Take me back to the most
life changing conversation that you've ever had.
What is the greatest advice that
you ever received throughout your career?
Well, that's a weird thing to say because
it's you have to understand the way that I'm
wired.
But may God have mercy
upon my enemies because I won't.
There's no mercy for the competition.
No, there's no mercy for the competition.
Listen, there's such things as friendly competition.
And there are lots of people
that I compete with that I respect.
But then there's, listen, when you build something
great and you build something and you're making
money, everybody's coming.
Everybody's coming for you to try to
take a piece or take you down.
And if you don't jump out of bed every day
and strap up and get ready to go to war, you're
never going to make it.
Being an entrepreneur is a war every day.
You have to go to battle and you got
to be willing to get in there and fight.
Not just in business, but in life.
Bad shit's coming for you.
And every day bad things happen here
and bad people come at you every day.
And if you don't look at it as, all right,
this is a fight and we need a winner and a
loser and I need to figure out how to
win, it's going to be a rough go for you.
What anyone else thinks.
Come on.
I love it.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Thank you so much, man.
I appreciate you, man.
Pleasure.
You're a massive inspiration.
Thank you.
I really appreciate that.
You here for the fights this weekend?
Yes, sir.
I'll be here.
You going to slap?
Yes, sir.
This is your first slap?
First slap.
Yeah.
So when you were asking about mentality and what
it, since I was a kid, this is the
quote that I've lived my whole life by.
Read that and tell me that doesn't make sense.
Because you might as well be dead.
Seriously, you always put limits on what
you could do, physical or anything else.
It'll spread into your life.
Literally every day when you get out of bed,
you try to be better than you were yesterday.
And I don't know how old you
are, whether it's physically, prove your relationships
or your business.
How did we beat yesterday?
That's literally the way that I think.
Yeah.
And what I do.
Yep.
Let's just say it to them right here.
What does it say?
Everybody pities the weak.
Jealousy is earned.
I love that man.
Don't be the weak.
She's going to give you my cell number and
then text me and let me know it too.
Congrats.
Dana, thank you so much.
I really had it for you, man.
Thank you for letting us come out of it.
Guys, that's a wrap on today's video.
We just interviewed the legendary Dana White.
Did the interview.
He gave us a tour.
That's a legend right there.
I need you all to do me a huge favor.
Like and subscribe, man.
Because every week I'm doing the craziest things.
I'm going to bring you all the biggest business
owners in the world to get their advice for
you.
But let's take things a step further.
I want to help you out even more because
look, I actually give you direct access to the multimillionaires
and the billionaires I interview on this channel
every single week because I launched and built
a private community for entrepreneurs where you
can ask your questions directly to the
millionaires and billionaires I interview
on this channel every week inside.
All you have to do to join is go
down, click the link in the description of this video.
I can't wait to see you on the inside.
With that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.